<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>123 Hugo</title>
    <link>//123.com/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on 123 Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 | 123 Hugo</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//123.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Armadillo</title>
      <link>//123.com/1/armadillo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//123.com/1/armadillo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Armadillos are New World placental mammals with a leathery armor shell. The Chlamyphoridae and Dasypodidae are the only surviving families in the order Cingulata, part of the superorder Xenarthra, along with the anteaters and sloths. The word armadillo means &amp;lsquo;little armored one&amp;rsquo; in Spanish.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cow</title>
      <link>//123.com/2/cow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//123.com/2/cow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cows are the most common type of large domesticated ungulates. They are a prominent modern member of the subfamily Bovinae, are the most widespread species of the genus Bos, and are most commonly classified collectively as Bos taurus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bat</title>
      <link>//123.com/1/bat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//123.com/1/bat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bats are mammals of the order Chiroptera whose forelimbs form webbed wings, making them the only mammals naturally capable of true and sustained flight. Bats do not flap their entire forelimbs, as birds do, but instead flap their spread out digits.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon</title>
      <link>//123.com/2/dragon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//123.com/2/dragon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A dragon is a legendary creature, typically scaled or fire spewing and with serpentine, reptilian or avian traits, that features in the myths of many cultures around world. The two most well known cultural traditions of dragon are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The European dragon, derived from European folk traditions and ultimately related to Balkans and Western Asian mythologies. Most are depicted as reptilian creatures with animal level intelligence, and are uniquely six limbed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Chinese dragon, with counterparts in Japan, Korea and other East Asian and South Asian countries. Most are depicted as serpentine creatures with above average intelligence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>